<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE section PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY % BOOK_ENTITIES SYSTEM "Installation_Guide.ent">
<!ENTITY PRODUCT "Fedora">
<!ENTITY NEXTVER "21">
<!ENTITY PRODVER "20">
<!ENTITY PREVVER "19">
<!ENTITY BOOKID "install-guide">
<!ENTITY YEAR "2014">
<!ENTITY HOLDER "Red Hat, Inc. and others">
<!ENTITY BZURL "https://bugzilla.redhat.com/enter_bug.cgi?product=&PRODUCT;&amp;component=&BOOKID;">
<!ENTITY IGURL '<ulink url="http://docs.fedoraproject.org/" />'>
]>
<section id="sect-installation-gui-root-password">
	<title>Root Password</title>
	<para>
		The <guilabel>Root Password</guilabel> screen is used to configure the <systemitem class="username">root</systemitem> password for your system. This password will be used to log into the administrator (also known as superuser) account, which is used for system administration tasks such as installing and updating software packages and changing system-wide configuration such as network and firewall settings, storage options and adding or modifying users, groups and file permissions.
	</para>
	<para>
	    The <systemitem class="username">root</systemitem> account will always be created during the installation. However, you should always also create a normal user accont in <ulink url="UserSpoke.xml">Create User</ulink> and use that account to log in to the system. Only switch to the administrator account only when you need to perform a task which requires administrator access.
	</para>
	<warning>
        <para>
            The <systemitem class="username">root</systemitem> account has complete control over the system. If an unauthorized person gains access to this account, access or delete all users' personal files or otherwise exploit the machine for their own nefarious purposes. See the <citetitle>Fedora Security Guide</citetitle>, available at the <ulink url="http://docs.fedoraproject.org/">Fedora Documentation website</ulink>, for detailed documentation about account security and guidelines for choosing a strong password.
        </para>
    </warning>
	<para>
	    </para>
	<para>
	    Once you choose a strong password, enter it in the <guilabel>Root Password</guilabel> field. The characters you write will be displayed as dots for security. Then, type the same password into the <guilabel>Confirm</guilabel> field to ensure you entered it properly. Both entered passwords must be the same.
	</para>
	<para>
	    As you enter the password, it will be evaluated and the installer will determine the password's strength. If the installer considers your password weak, a message will appear at the bottom of the screen, explaining which aspect of your chosen password is considered insuficient. For example:
	</para>
	<screen>
<guilabel>The password you have provided is weak:</guilabel> <guilabel>The password is shorter than 5 characters.</guilabel>
	</screen>
	<para>
	    If a message similar to the above appears, it is highly recommended to choose a different, stronger password.
	</para>
	<para>
	    Once you configure the superuser password, click <guilabel>Done</guilabel> in the top left corner to return to the </para>
</section>
